<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2023-11-29T15:34:58+00:00</updated><id>https://murli-dhwani.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">29th November 2023 sakaar Murli</title><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="29th November 2023 sakaar Murli"/><published>2023-11-29T05:05:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-29T05:05:00+00:00</updated><id>https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/"><![CDATA[<figure> <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3AYvKpApDJI?si=szubITAyBizLyi2i" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="" width="auto" height="auto"/> </figure> <h1 id="essence">Essence:</h1> <p>Sweet children, make your intellects and thoughts so pure and clean that you can imbibe shrimat accurately and thereby glorify the Father’s name.</p> <h1 id="question">Question:</h1> <p>Which stage of you children will show (reveal) the Father?</p> <h1 id="answer">Answer:</h1> <p>When your stage is such that your faces are constantly cheerful, that you are unshakeable and immovable and you remain stable and intoxicated, you will then be able to reveal the Father. Such clever children with a constant stage are able to give everyone the Father’s introduction accurately.</p> <h1 id="essence-for-dharna">Essence for dharna:</h1> <ol> <li> <p>Make your stage unshakeable and immovable and one of great intoxication. Keep your face constantly cheerful.</p> </li> <li> <p>Remain in the pure pride of this knowledge and reveal the Father. Prove who the God of the Gita is and give everyone the true introduction of the Father.</p> </li> </ol> <h1 id="blessing">Blessing:</h1> <p><strong>May you be a true server and, as an embodiment of remembrance, remind souls of themselves.</strong></p> <p>Using your features of an embodiment of remembrance, to make others into embodiments of remembrance, is to do true service. Let your features remind others that they are souls and that when they look at someone’s forehead, let them see the sparkling soul or jewel. Just as when people see the jewel on a snake, their attention does not go to the snake itself, in the same way, seeing the imperishable, sparkling jewel, let them forget body consciousness and their attention automatically go to the soul. Let those who have forgotten this become aware and you will then be said to be a true server.</p> <h1 id="slogan">Slogan:</h1> <p>Destroy the intellect that imbibes defects and adopt a satopradhan and divine intellect.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="videos"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is what included videos could look like]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">28th November 2023 sakaar Murli</title><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="28th November 2023 sakaar Murli"/><published>2023-11-28T05:05:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-28T05:05:00+00:00</updated><id>https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/"><![CDATA[<figure> <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sZsSnDfT71I?si=gKc_qvARkIzTy_7W" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="" width="auto" height="auto"/> </figure> <h1 id="essence">Essence:</h1> <p>Sweet children, this knowledge is butter and devotion is buttermilk. The Father gives you butter in the form of this knowledge and makes you into the masters of the world. This is why they show butter in the mouth of Shri Krishna.</p> <h1 id="question">Question:</h1> <p>How can you recognise someone whose intellect has faith? What attainment is there on the basis of faith?</p> <h1 id="answer">Answer:</h1> <ol> <li>The children whose intellects have faith are the true moths who surrender themselves to the Flame, not those who simply circle around. Only those who surrender themselves to the Flame enter the kingdom. Those who simply circle around become part of the subjects.</li> <li>The promise of the children whose intellects have faith is: “Even in the most adverse situations, I will not let go of my religion.” Their intellects have true love and so they forget all their bodily religions and their bodies and stay in remembrance of the Father.</li> </ol> <h1 id="essence-for-dharna">Essence for dharna:</h1> <ol> <li> <p>Become a Shiv Shakti and benefit the world. On the basis of purity, change human beings who are worth shells and make them worth diamonds.</p> </li> <li> <p>According to shrimat, donate the vices and become fully viceless, 16 celestial degrees full. Become the moths who surrender themselves to the Flame.</p> </li> </ol> <h1 id="blessing">Blessing:</h1> <p><strong>May you become a powerful soul and an embodiment of remembrance while overcoming adverse situations by considering them to be “side scenes.”</strong></p> <p>Because souls who are embodiments of remembrance are powerful, they consider adverse situations to be games. No matter how big the situations may be, for powerful souls, all of those are “side scenes” on the path to their destination. People actually spend money to go and see “side scenes.” For powerful souls who are embodiments of remembrance, whether you call it an adverse situation, a paper or an obstacle, all of them are side scenes. You are aware that you have passed those “side scenes” on the way to your destination countless times; it is nothing new.</p> <h1 id="slogan">Slogan:</h1> <p>Instead of correcting others, make a connection with the Father and you will continue to experience blessings.</p> <h1 id="sweet-elevated-versions-of-mateshwari">Sweet elevated versions of Mateshwari</h1> <p><strong>There is no benefit in just chanting the mantra of “om”.</strong></p> <p>To chant “om” means to sing this constantly. When we say the word “om”, it does not mean that we have to say it out loud. There is no benefit in life by simply saying “om”. However, by being stable in the meaning of “om” and by knowing the meaning of that word “om”, human beings can have peace in their lives. People definitely want to have peace, and they have many conferences to establish that peace. However, the result seen is that there is greater peacelessness and causes of sorrow. The main reason is that there cannot possibly be peace on earth until human beings have destroyed the five vices. So first, every human being has to control their five vices and connect the strings of their souls to the Supreme Soul; only then can there be peace. So, let each person ask the self: Have I destroyed the five vices in me? Have I made the effort to conquer them? If they ask, “How can I control the five vices in me?” show them this method. First of all, give the dhoop (fragrance from incense sticks) of this knowledge and yoga. Then, together with that, tell them the elevated versions of the Supreme Soul: Connect the yoga of your intellect to Me, take power from Me and by your remembering Me, the Almighty Authority, God, the vices will continue to be removed. We now have to make this much spiritual endeavour, that God Himself comes and teaches us. Achcha.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="videos"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is what included videos could look like]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">27th November 2023 sakaar Murli</title><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="27th November 2023 sakaar Murli"/><published>2023-11-27T05:05:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-27T05:05:00+00:00</updated><id>https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/"><![CDATA[<figure> <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8l1_QmIFnMo?si=z5AAr9fr8KxNtzHb" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="" width="auto" height="auto"/> </figure> <h1 id="essence">Essence:</h1> <p>Sweet children, during the day, perform actions for the livelihood of your bodies and sit down at night and churn this knowledge. Remember the Father. Make your intellects spin the discus of self-realisation and your intoxication will rise.</p> <h1 id="question">Question:</h1> <p>Which children does Maya not allow to sit in remembrance?</p> <h1 id="answer">Answer:</h1> <p>Maya doesn’t allow those to sit in remembrance whose intellects are trapped in someone or other, whose intellects are locked and who don’t study well. They are unable to remain “Manmanabhav”. Then their intellects don’t work for service either. Because of not following shrimat, they defame the Father’s name and deceive Him and so punishment has to be experienced.</p> <h1 id="essence-for-dharna">Essence for dharna:</h1> <ol> <li> <p>Do the spiritual service of making human beings become like diamonds. Never let your intellect develop doubts and thereby stop studying. Remain a trustee.</p> </li> <li> <p>While acting for the livelihood of your body, you have to remember the Father. Continue to move along while considering there to be benefit for you in following shrimat. Do not follow the dictates of your own mind.</p> </li> </ol> <h1 id="blessing">Blessing:</h1> <p><strong>May you be an intense effort-maker and use the powers of thought and speech accurately and powerfully.</strong></p> <p>Intense effort-makers, that is, the children who are going to go into the first division use the power of thought and the power of speech accurately and powerfully; they do not become loose in this. They always remember the slogan: Speak less, speak softly, speak sweetly. Their every word is yogyukt and yuktiyukt. They only speak the words that are necessary and they do not waste their energy in speaking wasteful words or words of expansion. They constantly stay in solitude.</p> <h1 id="slogan">Slogan:</h1> <p>A complete destroyer of attachment is one who even renounces any right to the consciousness of “mine”.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="videos"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is what included videos could look like]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">26th November 2023 Avyakt Murli</title><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/avyakt/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="26th November 2023 Avyakt Murli"/><published>2023-11-26T05:05:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-26T05:05:00+00:00</updated><id>https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/avyakt</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/avyakt/"><![CDATA[<figure> <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/q8ePrSd7ZxI?si=Yi22_f51jX-jSFCl" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="" width="auto" height="auto"/> </figure> <h1 id="in-the-new-year-become-an-embodiment-of-experience-and-make-others-experienced">In the New Year, become an embodiment of experience and make others experienced.</h1> <p>Today, BapDada, the One who takes you beyond with a glance, is seeing you deeply loving and co-operative children who are absorbed in love. The proof of love is visible on each child’s forehead and in his heart. (Speaking to the brothers and sisters sitting at the back of the hall.) You may think that BapDada cannot see those of you who are sitting at the back, but BapDada has such a unique TV that scenes far away are visible to His eyes as being very close. You may be sitting in a corner somewhere, but you are in front of the Father. Now, you are at least sitting very comfortably. Today, you have a lot of zeal, enthusiasm and happiness and so you are showing that by applauding, but BapDada knows the happiness in your hearts. BapDada is seeing that each child has a lot of happiness in giving the proof of co-operation, and this is why a thousand arms have been shown. The arms are a symbol of co-operation. BapDada knows that each of you children everywhere, whether in this land or abroad, whether through his mind, body or wealth, has definitely given co-operation, and that, as proof of that co-operation, you are today sitting comfortably and seeing and listening to everything in the hall. Now, do not clap so much! The clapping of happiness in each one’s mind has reached BapDada.</p> <p>Today, there are two specialities. One is this Shantivan that all of you have created with zeal and enthusiasm. Today, all of you children are inaugurating it with BapDada. Secondly, according to the drama, the New Year is also about to begin. Therefore, BapDada is embracing all of you, His children, in His two arms and congratulating you for both these occasions. Just as, at present, you are dancing with zeal, enthusiasm and happiness with the Father in the corporeal form, in the same way, in the New Year, in the avyakt form consider yourselves to be companions - experience this. The experience of this companionship is very lovely. BapDada does not like to be without the children. (The microphone stopped working.) This is the first experience. Therefore, consider this to be a game in the drama. Do not consider it to be something wrong. Everything is good and everything will be good. While saying that everyone is very good, you will also become good and every scene of the drama will become good, because the vibrations of your becoming good will change any scene, even if it is negative, into positive. You children have so much power; simply use it. You have many powers and by using them at the right time, you will have very good experiences.</p> <p>This is a new hall and it is the New Year, so what will you do in it? You will bring about some newness in the New Year, will you not? This year is the year to become an embodiment of experience and to give others experience. Do you understand what you have to do? You have to experience all of this. You are already using words, but every child now has to experience every power and every virtue. You are images of experience, are you not? Are you embodiments of experience or embodiments of words? You are experienced, but this year, let no child say that he has the experience of some aspects, but lacks the experience of some other aspect. Let there be no such child, because this knowledge does not mean just to understand, but also to experience it, for you cannot make others experience something unless you have experienced it yourself. If you have just reached the stage of words but do not have the experience, then the souls for whom you become an instrument to serve will also say, “It is very good, it is very good, it is a wonder.” They will only come that far. However, there are very few souls out of multimillions who become experienced, and the basis of revelation is experience. Souls who have experience will never be influenced by the atmosphere or be coloured by some company. Those who are influenced by words sometimes dance, whereas at other times they will begin to have many thoughts. Experience means to have a strong foundation. If the experience is incomplete, then the foundation is also only half strong. The sign of this is that they fluctuate over little things. They would not be unshakeable, because the situations that come or the problems that come become stronger. This is why those whose foundation is incomplete limp along. They do not fall, but they simply limp along. So, this year, first of all, strengthen your foundation of being an embodiment of experience. While moving along, some children may be very fast today, but their faces tomorrow would have changed a little. The reason is that their foundation of experience is not strong. Souls who are experienced will solve even the greatest problems as though nothing has happened. It came and it played its part, but they would consider it to be a game while being loving and detached observers. It was not a big situation, but a game. It was just entertainment. You like entertainment, do you not? No matter what the situation is, it is a big thing for you when the foundation is even slightly weak. Even if it is 75% or 90% strong, there is still a possibility for the foundation to shake. BapDada does not like to see you children work hard or battle. Why should you work hard? Why should you battle? Instead of being yogi souls, are you those who become warriors? Or, are you yogi souls? Sanskars of battling will take you into the moon dynasty, whereas the sanskars of a yogi soul will take you into the sun dynasty. So, what do you want to become: sun dynasty or moon dynasty? If you wish to become part of the sun dynasty, then let all battling finish. This year, has your battling finished? You didn’t say “Yes” to this! You only said “Yes” when Baba asked you whether it has finished. BapDada sees the result of the children, even while not seeing it. The result of every moment is not in front of the eyes, but it emerges in Baba’s heart. When you fluctuate here, in the corporeal world, either a little or a lot, BapDada experiences in the subtle region that someone is fluctuating. Therefore, just as you have the happiness of Shantivan and this hall, in the same way, promise, in front of BapDada and this huge gathering, that this year you have go beyond all upheavals and that you have to become unshakeable and immovable: not that you will become that, but that you have to become that. Is it like this? Those of you who feel that you have to become this, not that you will think about it, or that you will do it, raise your hands! Raise your hands high! Achcha, congratulations! Those of you who did not raise your hands due to any reason, it is impossible that you will not become this. However, if you did not raise your hand due to any reason, raise your hand now! Are you ashamed to raise it? In that case think about it: when you are too ashamed to raise your hand, you should also feel ashamed at the time of doing it (fluctuating). When you think that this is something to be ashamed about, you will not do it and so you will become strong. Some children ask BabaDada and the instrument children, again and again, in their heart-to-heart conversations, the same question: Baba, tell us the date of destruction. Do all of you have this question? Achcha, if BapDada gives you the date and says that there will be completion in the year 2000, what would you do then? Baba is not giving you a date, so let there not be any misunderstanding. BapDada is asking you that if He were to tell you that everything will finish by 2000, what would you do then? Would you become careless or intense effort-makers? You would become intense effort-makers. However, if BapDada says that this year there will be upheaval, what would you do then? Would you become even more intense effort-makers? Or, would you become a little date conscious and count that one year has now gone by, another month has now gone by. So, would you become date conscious or soul conscious? What would you do? You would not become careless, would you? Or, would you think that you still have four years, and so it doesn’t matter and that you will make effort in the last year. You would not become careless in this way, would you? Or, would you be a little careless? Even if you do not become careless, Maya is listening to you, and she will bring such things in front of you that carelessness and laziness will creep in now and then. So, what would you do then? This is why BapDada also told you earlier not to become date conscious but to consider every moment to be the last moment and to be ever ready at every moment. OK, BapDada may say that it will happen after 2000; you may accept that. Although it is not like that, you accepted it, and so you will become complete by the year 2000. So, when will you make others complete? In the golden age? Will you make others complete in the golden age? There are a few who make others that and many who become that. Do you need time for them or not? Last season too, Baba asked whether you had created the minimum population of the golden age of 900,000. If you have not created them yet, how can destruction take place? Whom would you rule over? Would you rule over old souls? The new souls are not ready yet, so if destruction were to take place, what would you do then? This is why BapDada has kept this work for His children who are fortune-tellers. Why should the Father do the work that fortune-tellers do? They too are the Father’s children. Let them earn their income. This is their means of income. If someone is in a great hurry to find out, then ask those children! The Father will not tell you.</p> <p>Do you understand what you have to do this year? Become embodiments of experience! Many children have sweet heart-to-heart conversations and they say, “Baba, what can we do? So much has already been accomplished, and so You can do the rest. We will rule, but You have to make us perfect.” Will this do? The Father is definitely your Helper and will be till the end. This is a guarantee, but whose Helper will He be? The Father will totally help those who take the first step of courage. The Father will then help you fully to take the second step of help. If you do not take a step of courage, but simply tell Baba, “Baba, You do this, You do this”, then BapDada would also say: I shall see, but at least take the first step! How can anything happen if you do not even take one step? This is why, this year, check at every moment that your steps of courage are strong. Check before you ask the Father. It is impossible that when you take a step of courage Baba would not help. Simply take a step of courage. This is why it is said: When the child has courage, the Father helps. Do not take this the wrong way and think that the Father helps and then the children have the courage. The Father continues to smile and say, Wah! My children! Wah! My beloved children! If you take a step of courage with faith, Baba is ready to give multimillion-fold help to every one of you children at every moment.</p> <p>What else will you do in the New Year? Even now, one aspect of service still remains. What is that? The God of the Gita has to be proved. However, BapDada told every zone last year that you have created and will continue to create many loving and co-operative souls who are in connection with you, but that you now have to create heirs. Very few heirs are emerging. BapDada sees the result at every centre every day. In all directions, the result is that there are very few heirs and many loving and co-operative souls. However, you have to make them move forward. Bring new ones and enable these last ones to go fast and thereby bring heir-quality souls in front of the Father. Very few heir souls emerge – just those that you can count. Since you want transformation to take place by 2000, and that’s what everyone wants, how many heirs have you created? The people of the golden age have to be royal, and there are very few of those. You have created subjects. You have had many types of conferences and have been invited to many outside programmes. This year, the result of the impact - the subjects - is good, but what does BapDada want? Now prepare heir-quality souls. Only when you bring heirs here will the advance party be revealed. Then the drums of revelation of the Father’s name will beat in all directions. In the result so far, you are doing very good work. Some say that only you can do this. They even say this, but their attention now needs to be drawn to the Supreme Soul. It is still incognito that the task of God is being carried out. Because of your power and love, you children are making very good efforts to reveal the Father. However, while they are still only loving and co-operative, the revelation of the Father cannot take place. It is good that you have arrived at this point, but the sound, “It is now the time, the Father has come”, has to emerge from everyone’s lips. Then destruction will also take place. The Father says: Do not ask the Father when destruction will take place. The Father is asking you when you will be ready. Should the curtains be opened? Are you ready for the curtains to open? Or, will the curtains open and you will still be continuing to get ready? At least reveal 16,108 firm strong jewels! At least create the rosary! The Father is also seeing whether the rosary is ready. There is this much margin. Baba is not asking for a lot. He is not asking for 900,000, but for you to create a rosary of 16,108. Therefore, create it this year. We shall see whether the unshakeable rosary of 16,108 who are free from obstacles is ready. Or, are you still limping along a little and showing your games a little? What do you Pandavas think? Are you ready? Speak! The Dadis are saying, “Yes”. Are the Shaktis saying, “Yes, the rosary of 16,108 is ready.”? Achcha, prepare the rosary by the 18th. If Baba were to ask you to raise your hands, half the gathering would say that you are part of the 16,108. Those of you who think that they are in this rosary, give a little note to the Dadis saying whether you are in the 16,000 or in the 108. The Dadis will then validate this. Do not think that, just because you have given your name on a piece of paper, that’s it. First, they will pass it, then BapDada will pass it and you will then be given the final result. Achcha.</p> <p>To those in all directions who are moving forward with zeal and enthusiasm, to those who become incarnations of economy and accumulate their time, thoughts, words and actions in their savings accounts, to those who celebrate the New Year in the corporeal and subtle forms, to the long-lost and now-found children, BapDada is seeing that children in all directions - if not in the corporeal form, then in the subtle form - are in Madhuban, and are celebrating in the subtle form, and so, Baba is congratulating everyone for the establishment of Shantivan and for the New Year and is giving love, remembrance and namaste to all the jewels of contentment.</p> <h1 id="blessing">Blessing:</h1> <p><strong>May you be free and free from bondage and finish all bondages by having the awareness of your original and eternal form.</strong></p> <p>The original and eternal form of each soul is freedom – being a master. Souls became dependent later. Therefore, become free from bondage by keeping your original and eternal form in your awareness. Let there be no bondage in your mind either. If there is any bondage in your mind, that bondage will bring other bondages. To be free from bondage means to be a king, a master of oneself, a self-sovereign. Such souls who are free from bondage and liberated will pass with honours, that is, they will go into the first division.</p> <h1 id="slogan">Slogan:</h1> <p>To be a master remover of sorrow and transform sorrow into spiritual happiness is to do true service.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="videos"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is what included videos could look like]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">25th November 2023 sakaar Murli</title><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="25th November 2023 sakaar Murli"/><published>2023-11-25T05:05:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-25T05:05:00+00:00</updated><id>https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/"><![CDATA[<figure> <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/osrQowadDpo?si=w99MtxMdl4oGd1Iu" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="" width="auto" height="auto"/> </figure> <h1 id="essence">Essence:</h1> <p>Sweet children, become nightingales of knowledge and continue to sing knowledge throughout the day and you will be able to show (reveal) your physical and spiritual mothers and fathers.</p> <h1 id="question">Question:</h1> <p>It is said: Grind your own ingredients and your intoxication will rise. What is the meaning of this?</p> <h1 id="answer">Answer:</h1> <p>To grind your own ingredients means not to let your intellect’s yoga wander here and there, but to remember the one Father. If only the one Father remains in your intellect, your intoxication can rise. However, body consciousness causes a lot of obstacles in this. When some are even a little ill, they become distressed. They begin to remember their friends and relatives and this is why their intoxication doesn’t rise. If they were to stay in yoga, their pain would lessen.</p> <h1 id="essence-for-dharna">Essence for dharna:</h1> <ol> <li> <p>In order to save yourself from Maya, a ghost, remain busy in this knowledge and yoga. Renounce the evil spirit of attachment and show the Father. Sing knowledge.</p> </li> <li> <p>Pay full attention to studying and claim your inheritance from the Father. Under no circumstances should you lose this chance every cycle.</p> </li> </ol> <h1 id="blessing">Blessing:</h1> <p><strong>May you be the master of yourself by becoming rup and basant, that is, by being gyani and yogi according to the time.</strong></p> <p>Those who are masters of themself can become rup when they want and basant when they want. They can create either of the two stages in a second. Let it not be that you want to become rup but that you keep remembering things of knowledge instead. Put a full stop in less than a second. A powerful brake works when it is applied. For this, practise stabilising your mind and intellect in whatever stage you want at whatever time you want. Let there be such controlling and ruling powers.</p> <h1 id="slogan">Slogan:</h1> <p>A messenger of peace is one who gives the gift of peace to those who bring storms.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="videos"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is what included videos could look like]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">24th November 2023 sakaar Murli</title><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="24th November 2023 sakaar Murli"/><published>2023-11-20T05:05:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-11-20T05:05:00+00:00</updated><id>https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2023/sakaar/"><![CDATA[<figure> <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iRUvrGvLpVk?si=IzKdeoJcs4H-x8J8" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="" width="auto" height="auto"/> </figure> <h1 id="essence">Essence:</h1> <p>Sweet children, only when there is cleanliness and honesty in your hearts will the arrow of the true things you say strike the target. You now have the company of the true Father, therefore, be honest and truthful.</p> <h1 id="question">Question:</h1> <p>What is it essential for you students to be cautious about?</p> <h1 id="answer">Answer:</h1> <p>Whenever you make a mistake, you have to tell the truth. It is only by telling the truth that you will make progress. You mustn’t take personal service from others. If you take service here, you will have to serve there. You students have to study well and teach others, because only then will the Father be pleased. The Father is the Ocean of Love and His love is that He educates you children and gives you a high status.</p> <h1 id="essence-for-dharna">Essence for dharna:</h1> <ul> <li> <p>Give the return of love of the Father, the Ocean of Love. Study well and teach others. You have to follow shrimat.</p> </li> <li> <p>First of all, imbibe knowledge with honesty and a clean heart and then inspire others to imbibe it. Stay in the company of the one Father.</p> </li> </ul> <h1 id="blessing">Blessing:</h1> <p><strong>May you become sensible and free of sins by knowing the importance of the directions given by the instrument souls.</strong></p> <p>Sensible children will never think that perhaps the directions being given by the instrument souls are given because of someone saying something to them. Never have such waste thoughts about the instrument souls. Even if someone makes a decision that you do not like, you are not responsible for that and so you will not accumulate sin in that because it is the Father who made that one an instrument and He can change that sin. This significance is incognito; it is incognito machinery.</p> <h1 id="slogan">Slogan:</h1> <p>An honest person loves God and loves the world, not one who loves to rest.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="videos"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is what included videos could look like]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog</title><link href="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog"/><published>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</updated><id>https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://murli-dhwani.github.io/blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry></feed>